José "Limón" Pérez

Mexico City, Federal District, Mexico



linkedin.com/in/jos%C3%A9-%E2%80%9Clim %C3%B3n%E2%80%9D-p%C3%A9rez-64a263166



jmpp97@gmail.com

Summary

Experienced Application Developer with a demonstrated history of working in the arts and crafts industry, AR and VR videogame development, advertisement videogame industry and web services development. Skilled in Unity, Python (Programming Language), C++, Java, and C (Programming Language). Strong engineering professional with a Licentiate degree focused in Videogame programming from Sae Institute Mexico.

Experience

Application Developer

Baud

Aug 2019 - Present (9 months +)



Application Developer

Self Employed

Jan 2007 - Present (13 years 4 months +)

Full-stack Developer

Factor Evolución S.A. de C.V.

Mar 2019 - Apr 2020 (1 year 2 months)

Application Programmer

Centro de Cultura Digital

Jan 2018 - Dec 2018 (1 year)

Education



Sae Institute Mexico

Licentiate degree, Videogame programming 2016 - 2019

Skills

Unreal Engine • Unity3D • C++ • C# • Java • Python • C • Godot • Game Development • Software Development